<!--
    This form is generated automatically from the parameters pluginspec.
    Please not not edit this file manually as it will be regenerated.
-->
<editor>
  <help>/commander/pages/@PLUGIN_NAME@/help?s=Administration&amp;ss=Plugins#ListInstances</help>
  <formElement>
    <type>entry</type>
    <property>config</property>
    <configuration>1</configuration>
    <propertyReference>/plugins/@PLUGIN_NAME@/project/ec_plugin_cfgs</propertyReference>
    <required>1</required>
    <documentation>Previously defined configuration for the plugin</documentation>
    <label>Configuration Name:</label>
  </formElement>
  <formElement>
    <type>textarea</type>
    <property>filter</property>
    <required>0</required>
    <htmlDocumentation>Filter expression used to filter resources. The filter expression must specify the field name,
a comparison operator, and the value used to filter them.<br/><br/>
The value must be a string, a number, or a boolean and the comparison operator must be either =, !=, &gt;, or &lt;.<br/>
For example, name != foobar-instance will exclude all Virtual Instances named foobar-instance.
</htmlDocumentation>
    <label>Filter:</label>
  </formElement>
  <formElement>
    <type>integer</type>
    <property>maxResults</property>
    <documentation>The maximum number of results per page that should be returned. If the number of available results is larger than maxResults, Compute Engine returns a nextPageToken that can be used to get the next page of results in subsequent list requests. Acceptable values are 0 to 500, inclusive. (Default: 500)
</documentation>
    <label>Max Results:</label>
    <requred>false</requred>
  </formElement>
  <formElement>
    <type>entry</type>
    <property>orderBy</property>
    <required>0</required>
    <documentation>Order used to sort results.

By default results are sorted in alphanumerical order of resource name. In addition results can be sorted in descending order of time stamp by using orderBy="creationTimestamp desc". This sorts results based on the creationTimestamp field in reverse chronological order (newest result first).

Currently, only sorting by name or creationTimestamp desc is supported.
</documentation>
    <label>Order By:</label>
  </formElement>
  <formElement>
    <type>entry</type>
    <property>resultProperty</property>
    <required>1</required>
    <documentation>Property Sheet used to store JSON representation of instances found.</documentation>
    <label>Result Property Sheet:</label>
    <value>/myJob/instances</value>
  </formElement>
</editor>